(Penny:)Hey, so I saw a movie trailer
the other day.
(Penny:)How could Batman
possibly fight Superman?
(Penny:)I mean, isn't that dumb?
(Bernadette:)Maybe he uses Kryptonite.
(Emily:)Well, Batman's got
a lot of money.
(Emily:)Maybe he builds a suit that can
do everything Superman can do.
(Penny:)No, no, no, no, no.
(Penny:)I've seen that movie.
It's called Iron Man.
(quietly):
What is happening?
(Howard:)I don't know.
(Raj:)But it's beautiful.
(Penny:)And now Ben Affleck
is Batman?
(Emily:)Oh, he was great in
Shakespeare in Love.
(Penny:)Ooh, we should watch that
next girls' night.
(Bernadette:)We could do a double feature
with the Leonardo DiCaprio
Romeo + Juliet.
(Penny:)Oh, I love me some Leo.
(Leonard:)And it's gone.
(Sheldon:)Oh, hello, everyone.
(Sheldon:)I am happy to report
I'm feeling much better.
(Leonard:)Good for you.
(muttering)
(Sheldon:)My fever is gone,
my sinuses are pressure-free,
(Sheldon:)and my mucus is as clear
as a Yosemite waterfall.